Ruei-Pu(Allen) Kou

North York, ON imakou@gmail.com - 905-966-3228

I am a team-worker and love to share new staffs with co-workers and I am also a solution provider. I have a few years of experience in Taiwan and I have front-end skill-set including HTML, CSS, SASS and JavaScript. I am a lifetime learner and always follow the trends of front-end during school time.

I am currently learning:

RESTful web service, React Native, GraphQL, MongoDB, JS test runner(Karma)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

DIGIM - Taipei, Taiwan - January 2014 to May 2014

Converting PSD to web pages(including RWD) using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript(JQuery)

Web Developer

Rexholiday - Taipei - July 2013 to December 2013

Web Developer

Webike.tw - Taipei, Taiwan - January 2013 to July 2013

Deploy EC2 services on AWS Converting ideas to mockup

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Programmer

Seneca College - Toronto, ON January 2015 to April 2017

Bachelor in Information mangerment

Hsing Wu University - Taipei, Taiwan August 2007 to August 2011

SKILLS

Html5 (3 years), CSS3 (3 years), Javascript/jQuery (2 years), React/Redux (Less than 1 year), Grid System(Bootstrap, SUSY) (3 years), RWD (3 years), Cross-browser compatibility (3 years), NodeJS(Express) (Less than 1 year), AWS(EC2/LAMP) (1 year), PHP/MySQL (Less than 1 year), PhotoShop (3 years), Wordpress (2 years), Git (1 year), SASS (3 years), Graphic Sprites Solution/Retina displaySolution (3 years), Understanding of SEO (3 years)